Kabao Thao

1800 Graham Ave W Unit 134, Saint Paul, MN 55116 Cell: (612) 222-8402 | kabao.thao@outlook.com

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATION

Seeks to bring 7 years of professional technical experiences to a full stack developer position in a goal-oriented, face-paced tech environment. Solid understanding of the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) and SQL Server. Proficient in Microsoft Suite, Business Object, SharePoint, Visio, Oracle, Service Now, Tableau, Salesforce.

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

• HTML5, CSS, Git, Visual Studio

EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst, Voya Financial, MN

September 2020 – Present

- Manage client's group contract provisions for Life, Disability, and Supplemental Health Voluntary products.
 - o Draft and maintain business requirements and align them with functional and technical requirements.
 - o Conduct user acceptance testing to meet functionality requirements.
 - o Identify and reconcile errors in client data to ensure accurate business requirements.

Business Analyst, Voya Financial, MN

September 2016 – Present

- Administer client implementation processes and provide technical support to maintain ongoing active customers' insurance plans.
 - o Engage clients to gather software requirements, business rules, and ensure alignment with internal teams.
 - o Develop and manage project plans, negotiate project deliverables and timing, resolve issues and coordinate communication for clients.

Business Analyst, Fairview Health Services, MN

April 2016 – August 2016

- Configure, maintain, and modify software applications. Complete coding and modification of the software with focus on user experience and optimal system performance.
 - o Support the implementation planning for application program requirements. Support the end-user and technical operations staff as required by providing excellent customer service.
 - o Proactively participates in IT workflow processes in incident management, IT service request management, and change control management.

Business Analyst, Native American Community Clinic, MN

January 2015 – March 2016

- Lead the Expanded Medical Services grant by monitoring all data management aspects of the assigned grant.
 - o Implement electronic medical record system workflow processes to improve clinic operations.
 - o Administer state grant funding and delegated board reports monthly to internal and external stakeholders.

Business Analyst, UnitedHealth Group, MN

May 2014 – January 2015

- Perform day to day management of agents contracts process for Medicare Supplemental Products.
 - o Responsible for various types of contract management and support all scenarios of account opening and maintenance requirements.
 - o Assist in extracting and manipulating large data on SQL databases.

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota, MN

June 2021 – present

• MERN Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Saint Mary's University of Minnesota, MN

May 2014 – December 2015

• Master of Arts in Health & Human Services Administration

Saint Olaf College, MN

September 2010 – May 2014

• Bachelor of Arts in Economics